<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui='urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder'
             xmlns:g='urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui'
             ui:generateFormat='com.google.gwt.i18n.rebind.format.PropertiesFormat'
             ui:generateKeys="com.google.gwt.i18n.server.keygen.MD5KeyGenerator"
             ui:generateLocales='en'>

    <ui:with field="res" type="com.jci.client.resource.CommonResource"/>
    <ui:with field="aboutRes" type="com.jci.client.resource.about.AboutResource"/>

    <g:HTMLPanel>
        <div class="{res.style.width} {res.style.white} {res.style.dragUp} {res.style.round}
            {res.style.content}">
            <div class="{res.style.actions}">
                <a ui:field="buttonCanada" class="{res.style.button_gray} {res.style.active}">
                    JCI Canada
                </a>
                <a ui:field="buttonQuebec" class="{res.style.button_gray}">
                    <ui:msg description="About > JCI Quebec City" meaning="JCI Ville de Québec">JCI Quebec City</ui:msg>
                </a>
            </div>

            <div ui:field="canada">
                <h1>
                    <ui:msg description="About > Title 1">
                        About JCI Canada
                    </ui:msg>
                </h1>
                <p>
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 1">
                        The Junior Chamber movement came into existence in Canada in 1923 with the formation of its first
                        chapter, the Young Men’s Section of the Winnipeg Board of Trade. Just as it was when it was founded
                        in St. Louis, the Junior Chamber movement in Canada involved organizing young people to meet their
                        needs in terms of learning and development, and in turn meeting both the current and future needs of
                        their community.
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 2">
                        In 1936 representatives from chapters across Canada met in Toronto on February 2 and wrote a
                        constitution that officially founded the Canadian Junior Chamber of Commerce. History is rich with
                        examples of JCI Canada members who have been actively involved in the success of the International
                        Junior Chamber. One of the most outstanding members was certainly Phil Pugsley of Montreal, Canada
                        who became the seventh JCI President in 1951. Pugsley envisioned the idea of a Senatorship which
                        could honour and recognize the achievements of exceptional members and could enable them to remain
                        in contact with the Junior Chamber movement throughout their life. Through his perseverance, the JCI
                        Senate was created in 1952 at the 7th JCI World Congress in Melbourne, Australia.
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <p class="{res.style.noBottomMargin}">
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 3">
                        On the organizational level, JCI Canada hosted and organized many events throughout the years,
                        where members from across the world participated in a wide variety of high-quality training courses
                        and
                        opportunities for networking and fellowship, namely:
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <ui:msg description="About > list congress > element 1">
                            6th World Congress, Montreal, 1951
                        </ui:msg>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <ui:msg description="About > list congress > element 2">
                            22nd World Congress, Toronto, 1967
                        </ui:msg>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <ui:msg description="About > list congress > element 3">
                            39th World Congress, Montreal, 1984
                        </ui:msg>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <ui:msg description="About > list congress > element 4">
                            Americas Conference, Edmonton 2003
                        </ui:msg>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <ui:msg description="About > list congress > element 5">
                            National Conventions since 1936
                        </ui:msg>
                    </li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 4">
                        Active participation in a local becomes the primary vehicle by which a member can explore the
                        opportunities offered by JCI.
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <p class="{res.style.noBottomMargin}">
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 5">
                        JCI is proud to offer opportunities in the following four areas:
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <b>
                            <ui:msg description="About > list type > element 1">
                                Individual development
                            </ui:msg>
                        </b>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>
                            <ui:msg description="About > list type > element 2">
                                Business development
                            </ui:msg>
                        </b>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>
                            <ui:msg description="About > list type > element 3">
                                Community Development
                            </ui:msg>
                        </b>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>
                            <ui:msg description="About > list type > element 4">
                                International Development
                            </ui:msg>
                        </b>
                    </li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 6">
                        The range of programs and projects that provide these opportunities to members varies depending on
                        the local organization, which itself is based on the preferences and desires of its members. Every
                        year,
                        JCI Canada awards prizes for the programs, specific projects and achievements of individuals, and
                        all
                        this emphasis on the variety of activities undertaken by the different sections of the JCI Canada.
                        Our
                        members are very active both in their local community by participating in activities that range from
                        the organization of training programs on trade and development staff, to participation in
                        international
                        conferences, to through participation in networking events and fundraising for various charities.
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 7">
                        We organize a number of national programs to encourage the development of leadership skills among
                        our
                        members and in their communities. Our flagship programs include the Outstanding Young Person Award
                        (TOYP) (which are among its former winners Margaret Atwood, the Honourable Jean Charest, and Wayne
                        Gretzky), the Best Business Plan Competition and Effective Speaking Competition. We hold regional
                        conferences across Canada, as well as a National Convention every year in September in which we
                        offer
                        meetings, training, competitions and activities that promote collegiality.
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 8">
                        Since their affiliation with the Junior Chamber movement, many Canadians have contributed to the
                        advancement of youth. In keeping with this tradition, JCI Canada is now a growing presence from
                        coast to
                        coast with 30 local chapters and more on the way.
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <p class="{res.style.noBottomMargin}">
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 9">
                        For more information, visit
                    </ui:msg>
                    <a href="http://www.jcicanada.com/" target="_blank">
                        <ui:attribute name="href" description="Href > JCI Canada"/>
                        <ui:msg description="About > link 1">
                            www.jcicanada.com
                        </ui:msg>
                    </a>.
                </p>
                <g:Image addStyleNames="{aboutRes.style.imgLogo}" resource="{aboutRes.jci_canada}" altText="JCI Canada Logo"/>
            </div>

            <div ui:field="quebec" style="display: none">
                <h1>
                    <ui:msg description="About > Title 2">
                        About JCI Quebec City
                    </ui:msg>
                </h1>
                <p>
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 10">
                        Established in 1987, JCI Quebec City was founded to provide the opportunity for young entrepreneurs
                        and professionals to expand their networks and to learn how to develop leadership and social skills.
                        Considered as an important actor in the community, JCI Quebec City organizes more than 50 activities
                        each year and, as a result, has an impact on the social economic landscape of the region by
                        promoting personal and professional development of Quebec City youth.
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 11">
                        In 2000, members from the Quebec City local chapter voted to adhere to the JCI movement to enhance
                        our capability to serve the community and to twin with organizations of similar values and purpose
                        both across Canada and the world. Since becoming a member, JCI Quebec City has sent delegates to
                        attend several national conventions, area conferences and the 13 past world congresses. Numerous
                        members held National Offices, two of which served as JCI Canada National President in 2008 and
                        2012. Our own François Begin is currently serving as JCI International Vice president assigned to
                        Europe.
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <p class="{res.style.noBottomMargin}">
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 12">
                        JCI Quebec City also won many awards throughout the years, thus proving its dynamism within the JCI
                        movement :
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <div class="{res.style.ulNoPoints}">
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <b>
                                <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 1 > b">
                                    Most Outstanding New JCI Organization in Canada
                                </ui:msg>
                            </b>
                            <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 1">
                                at JCI Canada National Convention
                            </ui:msg>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <ul>
                                <li>
                                    <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 2">
                                        Edmonton, Canada, May 15, 2003
                                    </ui:msg>
                                </li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <b>
                                <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 3 > b">
                                    Most Outstanding JCI Organization in Canada
                                </ui:msg>
                            </b>
                            <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 3">
                                at JCI Canada National Conventions
                            </ui:msg>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <ul>
                                <li>
                                    <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 4 > list 4 > element 1">
                                        Edmonton, Canada, May 15, 2003
                                    </ui:msg>
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 4 > list 4 > element 2">
                                        Quebec City, September 29, 2004
                                    </ui:msg>
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 4 > list 4 > element 3">
                                        Cap Breton, September 2005
                                    </ui:msg>
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 4 > list 4 > element 4">
                                        Toronto, September 2011
                                    </ui:msg>
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 4 > list 4 > element 5">
                                        Cranbrooke, September 2012
                                    </ui:msg>
                                </li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <b>
                                <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 5 > b">
                                    Most Outstanding New JCI Organization in the Americas
                                </ui:msg>
                            </b>
                            <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 5">
                                at Area Conferences
                            </ui:msg>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <ul>
                                <li>
                                    <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 6 > list 5 > element 1">
                                        Quito, Equator, May 19, 2003
                                    </ui:msg>
                                </li>

                                <li>
                                    <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 6 > list 5 > element 2">
                                        Sao Paulo, May 7, 2005
                                    </ui:msg>
                                </li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                    <ul>
                        <li>
                            <b>
                                <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 7 > b">
                                    Most Outstanding New JCI Organization in the World
                                </ui:msg>
                            </b>
                            <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 7">
                                at World Congress
                            </ui:msg>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <ul>
                                <li>
                                    <ui:msg description="About > list 3 > element 8">
                                        Copenhagen, Denmark, Nov, 2003
                                    </ui:msg>
                                </li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </div>
                <p>
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 13">
                        In 2004, JCI Quebec City hosted the National Convention after being part of JCI and JCI Canada for
                        only two years. Quebec City established a benchmark for conventions in Canada by offering VIP
                        treatment to all of our guests. JCI Quebec City maintains relationships with a number of external
                        organizations among local chapters and national organisations of the JCI movement.
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 14">
                        JCI Quebec City
                        being the only French speaking chapter in North America, contacts were also made with other junior
                        chambers of French background. Since 2005, JCI Quebec City though JCI Canada has become a member of
                        JCI’s Association Internationale des Jeunes Chambres Francophones (International Francophone Junior
                        Chambers Association). Finally, JCI Quebec City is twinned with JCI Calgary and JCI Reims to develop
                        relations that are mutually beneficial.
                    </ui:msg>
                </p>
                <p class="{res.style.noBottomMargin}">
                    <ui:msg description="About > paragraph 9">
                        For more information, visit
                    </ui:msg>
                    <a href="http://www.jccq.qc.ca/" target="_blank">
                        <ui:msg description="About > link 2">
                            www.jccq.qc.ca
                        </ui:msg>
                    </a>.
                </p>
                <g:Image addStyleNames="{aboutRes.style.imgLogo}" resource="{aboutRes.jccq}" altText="JCCQ Logo"/>
            </div>
        </div>
    </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>
